TAHUANA CIRATI

JR WEB DEVELOPER

- tahuana@gmail.com
- tahuana.com
- **** +1 (416) 428-0567
- ♥ Toronto ON Canada
- in tahuana-cirati
- n tahuana

▶ Profile

Junior web developer excited to hone my knowledge in JavaScript, Node.js, React, Express, Ruby and much more! I have 15 years of experience working on projects within IT and Oil & Gas industries, including 3 years as project analyst, and 6 years in software testing. Result-driven, attention to detail, and strong analytical skills. When not coding, I can be found reading or testing new delicious recipes.

Skills

LANGUAGES

JavaScript

Node.js

HTML

CSS

SQL

Ruby

DATABASES

MongoDB

PostgreSQL

FRAMEWORKS

Express

Rails

Bootstrap

LIBRARIES

jQuery

React

OTHERS

Project Management Software Testing

Languages

English

Portuguese

Education

Lighthouse Labs

Immersive Full-Stack Web Development Bootcamp 2017

IBMEC Business School

Postgraduate Project Management 2013

UFRJ - Federal University of Rio de Janeiro

Bachelor's Degree Computer Science 2001

▶ Projects

tahuana.com

Aug 2017 to Aug 2017

- My personal website.
- Developed using HTML, CSS and Bootstrap.

Pairwise Jul 2017 to Jul 2017

- A project-driven mentoring platform built for experienced devs and learners to collaborate and grow.
- Developed using Ruby on Rails and PostgreSQL.

Resource Wall

Jun 2017 to Jun 2017

- Allow learners to save learning resources like tutorials, blogs and videos in a central place that is publicly available to any user.
- Developed using HTML, EJS, jQuery, AJAX, JavaScript and Sass in front-end, and Node, Express, PostgreSQL and Knex in back-end.

Tweeter Jun 2017 to Jun 2017

- Tweeter is a simple, single-page Twitter clone.
- Developed using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery and AJAX in front-end, and Node, Express and MongoDB in back-end.

GGI Oct 2015 to Jun 20

- Project to restructure the individual metering segment for Supergasbras, including: system improvements and process revision (metering, billing, delivery, collection, customer records).
- Worked as PMO supporting Project Manager on methodology, documentation, project schedule, and weekly status report.

Employment

Supergasbras Project Analyst Rio de Janeiro, Brazil Feb 2014 to Jun 2016

- Participated in the corporate PMO launching.
- Worked as team member of PMO group, supporting 7 projects simultaneously, within a program to ERP system implementation, to successful completion within the allocated time.
- Supported 10+ Project Managers in all aspects of the project lifecycle.

Supergasbras

Business Technology Analyst

Rio de Janeiro, Brazil Jun 2011 to Feb 2014

- Defined methodology and templates for software testing in Corporate IT.
- Led quality assurance of 5 softwares systems delivered by Corporate IT.
- Managed outsourced test team, including 4 professionals assigned in different projects.

Avanti Prima

System Analyst

Rio de Janeiro, Brazil Sep 2006 to Jun 2011

- Participated as tester analyst in 5 software development projects in Petrobras' IT.
- Led software quality assurance with one report, focusing on small projects.
- Trained new members on test team.

Certifications

PMI/PMP - Project Management Professional - 2013-2019

BSTQB/CTFL - Certified Tester, Foundation Level – From 2008